https://www.frys.com/template/help/index/FE30/Service3/Assistance/Middle_Topics/C3Privacy

Frys.com Help - Privacy Policy
FRY'S PRIVACY POLICY
Your privacy is important to us.
Fry's understands our customers' concerns regarding the privacy of the information they share with us. We hold our customers, and the information they share with us, in the highest regard. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. We are committed to ensuring that your personal information is properly safeguarded and to complying with all applicable federal and state privacy laws.
Please take a moment to read our Privacy Policy for a better understanding of the measures that we take to protect you and the information you share with us.
The following Privacy Policy describes information and privacy practices for Fry's Electronics, Inc. ("Fry's"), Fry's retail stores and Frys.com.
Please be aware that this site may contain links to other sites that are owned and operated by third parties.
This Privacy Policy may not apply to those links or to other sites.
These third party sites have their own privacy policies and practices.
We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these third party sites to learn how they collect, use, share and secure your information.
This Privacy Policy strives to encourage and maintain trust between you and Fry's.
As part of that trust, this Privacy Policy will tell you about:
What information we collect.
How information is used and protected.
How we may share information.
Choices you can make about how we collect, use, and share your information.
Future changes to the Privacy Policy.
What information do we collect?
Fry's collects information about you to provide the best products and services and to help Fry's improve your shopping experience both at Fry's retail stores and online at Frys.com.
Information you give us.
Fry's collects and may store any information you enter on our website, provide us in our retail stores, or submit to Fry's in any other way.
For example, we collect information that you provide when you create the myFry's Accounts on our website, make an online or in-store purchase from us, send us an e-mail or call us, enter a contest, or participate in a survey.
This information may include:
Your name.
Your mailing address.
Your e-mail address.
Your phone number.
Your credit card number.
On our website, there is an option to "Tell a Friend" about a product or service that we offer.
If you use Frys.com's "Tell a Friend" feature, we will use the e-mail address per your instructions to send your e-mail message to your friend. We will not use the e-mail address of your friend for any other purpose.
Information from other sources.
Fry's may receive information about you from other sources.
These other sources may help to improve the quality or personalization of services that we provide to you.
Automatic information.
We also receive and store certain types of information when you interact with our website.
Like many websites, we use "cookies" to obtain information when your web browser accesses our website.
The purpose of "cookies" is to help us recognize you as you use or return to our website so that we can provide a more personalized shopping experience for you.
The "cookie" is also used to keep items in your shopping cart between visits.
You do not need to enable cookies to browse, but must enable cookies to purchase items at Frys.com.
Our web server automatically collects clickstream information such as the address (or URL) of the website that you came from before visiting our site, which pages you visit on our site, which browser you used to view our site and any search terms you may have entered on our site, among other things.
Our website may also use other technologies to track which pages our visitors view. This anonymous clickstream data provides our customers with a better, more secure shopping experience and helps Fry's understand how visitors use our website.
Video Cameras
We operate cameras in and around Fry's stores for security and operational purposes.
These cameras are for security, operational and loss prevention purposes and we do not otherwise use these cameras to identify you personally.
How is information used and protected?
Our goal is to provide our customers with the highest level of service possible. From your first visit to our website to the delivery of your order, we want you to be completely satisfied with the experience without compromising your privacy. By collecting information, we are able to offer you features, such as our myFry's
Account (which saves you time during the order process), and a more customized website that better reflects your individual preferences.
Usage of Information
Fry's uses your information to provide requested products and services to you and to support general business operations.
Some examples of such usage includes:
To fulfill and process your orders and communicate with you regarding those orders.
To schedule and perform deliveries or installations.
To service products.
To send marketing communications.
To open and service your myFry's Accounts.
To provide high-quality customer service.
To help us improve and customize what we offer to you, our website and our advertising.
To send you information about our products, services and promotions.
To protect the security and integrity of our websites and our business.
To process credit card information.
Protection of Information
Fry's also protects your information from loss, misuse or alteration while it is under Fry's control.
Protection of your information is a priority at Fry's.
We have adopted reasonable security measures to protect the confidentiality of personal information under our control both online and in our stores.
When you enter personal information on our website, the information is protected by a security technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which encrypts your information during transport across the Internet.
Further, your account information is only accessible with the password you choose when you open the myFry's Accounts.
Please maintain the confidentiality of this password in order to ensure the protection of your account information.
How may information be shared?
Fry's does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties.
Fry's may share your personal information under the following limited circumstances:
Service Providers
We may provide your information to a third party in the process of fulfilling an order for products or services you have placed with us.
For example, we may provide your address to the shipping carrier where you have requested shipment for a purchase.
Fry's only shares the necessary information to third parties to provide the requested products or services in your order.
Credit Applications and Credit Card Processing
If you apply for a Fry's credit card, your information may be shared with First Electronic Bank to offer the credit card to you.
First Electronic Bank may use the information to provide the credit card and to service and maintain your credit card account.
Fry's may utilize third-party service providers to assist Fry's with processing credit card payments.
Legal Requirements and Safety of our Business and Others
Fry's may share information in other special circumstances.
We may disclose information where we have a good faith belief that disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law or where we believe disclosure is necessary to protect you, to comply with legal processes or authorities, to respond to any claims, or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of Fry's, its customers, its associates or the public.
This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction, and with analytics providers.
Marketing Purposes
Fry's may share information with carefully selected vendors and business partners who may share offers and opportunities with you based on your interests.
What are your choices regarding information?
Fry's wants to communicate with you to inform you of product specials, changes to our website, contests and surveys, or other information we think may be of interest to you.
Similarly, carefully selected vendors or business partners may want to communicate with you to inform you of special offers or opportunities.
If you do not wish to receive certain information or request that your information not be shared with third parties, please e-mail: service@cs.frys.com.
Please be sure to include your full name, the types of communication you would like to receive or not receive, and your related contact information.
Please note that even if you opt-out of receiving marketing communications from Fry's, you may still be contacted for transactional purposes.
Some examples include request for customer service or questions regarding your order.
How will you be notified of future changes to the Privacy Policy?
Fry's may change or add to its Privacy Policy from time to time.
For this reason, we encourage you to review the Privacy Policy periodically.
For your convenience, we will post the date it was last updated at the bottom of the Privacy Policy.
Privacy of Children Online
Fry's is committed to protecting children's online privacy and fully complies with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.
If you believe we may have collected personal information from a child, please e-mail us at service@cs.frys.com.
If you have any questions regarding the Privacy Policy, please e-mail: service@cs.frys.com.
Last Updated: September 25, 2020
jback115
